It's shining, you can see it ahead
The suit has a strong garlic flavor
Good morning everyone, I'm Aruno Nakanishi
It's currently 10 a.m. I am
I came to Matsuya for breakfast. I truly love Matsuya from the bottom of my heart
Today, unbelievably, this has become a YouTube project
I've arrived at Matsuya
Ta-da! I order a lot for delivery
I come alone, and I always get takeout too
Thank you! Now, let's get started
From here, I'll deliver with a voiceover. I entered Matsuya
The great thing about Matsuya, first, is that you can order with a touch panel
It's a very friendly way to order, especially for people like me who aren't good at communicating with staff
It's a very kind ordering method, and it really helps me
Since I'm recording this at 10 a.m., I'm really into the breakfast set
Matsuya's breakfast set is really delicious. It tastes like mom's cooking
It tastes like the breakfast my mom makes. But in the end, it's limited time only
I came today to eat this
I chose the tomato hamburger with stewed cabbage. I don't usually eat vegetables, so I don't pick set meals
I'll eat the set that comes with miso soup and rice
When this product came out, it was a hot topic because it looked like "Umatoma," so I was really looking forward to it
Since the day this job was decided, I've been holding back from eating it, so I was really excited
Total 880 yen, a great price. In Tokyo these days, a set meal easily goes over 1000 yen
I'm grateful. Heading to the seat in the back
I'm drinking a lot of water
But since it's this time of day, many people are ordering breakfast sets
Thank you
Wait, it's here
It smells strongly of garlic
With just one bite, I'm in the "Umatoma" mood
I truly love "Umatoma" from the bottom of my heart
If it's my peers, Teresa Ikeda, Hina Okamoto, and I introduced it, and they got hooked
Iroha Okuda, and Miku Ichinose, who said she likes garlic, might join the "Umatoma" club
I'm trying to recruit her now
Now, the fan group is split among the 5th generation
I'm working as the leading member in Nogizaka
It's so good, I'm shaking. Delicious
This is
Even though it's such a creamy color, it's packed with garlic. Morning
From 10 a.m., I consumed a lot of garlic
This is
About 80% "Umatoma." I feel a very mellow and mild "Umatoma"
I forgot to show everyone. Ta-da! I already took a bite
I'm not used to this, so I forgot to take a picture when it arrived
It's a rice show
I didn't order vegetables
Ah, I'm getting hungry
It's shining, it looks like a jewel
Matsuya's wonderful proof, it looked like a shining jewel
Delicious
Matsuya's side dishes are really
Rather salty, with a strong flavor
It's the kind that goes well with rice, a rich taste, and Matsuya's hamburger is really
Meaty, packed with meat
This product is definitely inspired by "Umatoma" from the Kazuki site
It's probably intentional, the introduction text is very promising
It's delicious, I might call the chef
The first time I ate "Umatoma," I almost stood up to call the chef
I'm not lying
The miso soup is strong
It tastes like grandma's miso soup
I want to see you
I want to see grandma
Another great thing about Matsuya, when you order a hamburger, you get a spoon
It's not cut with a fork and knife, it's a bit masculine
I really like it. I wonder if Matsuya has forks and knives
I might not know
Almost all the rice is gone. I eat pretty fast
I'm really quick, so
Quick entry, quick exit. I always head to Matsuya
If I had 30 minutes, I'd have plenty of time
I can finish quickly, so during work breaks
I sometimes drop by during work breaks
It's great that there are so many stores in Tokyo
For some reason, I want the tea with Matsuya's robot at home
It feels warm
Like a mother
By the way, I have something to reflect on
This
After eating the stewed cabbage tomato hamburger, I said it was a mellow "Umatoma"
in my food report
But for people who haven't eaten "Umatoma," they wouldn't understand
Comparing food to food, I did something taboo and I'm reflecting on it
It's a mellow but punchy hamburger with garlic from Matsuya
Probably, even when this video is released, another tomato dish will be out
But they never release "Umatoma" hamburger
I feel Matsuya's pride in that
"Umatoma" is a rare character that appears only once a year, and that's what makes it special
In the end, I keep eating things similar to "Umatoma," but
I always come back to the original "Umatoma"
Yeah
Ta-da! Finished eating
I'm full. It's been a while since I ate this much at 7:30
I ate a lot
Thank you
It was delicious, I'm full
I'm totally satisfied. After I get home
I'll just sleep