The food is here!
Delicious!
This is the best!
I want to eat a lot of them!
Cute!
I'm going to eat a lot today!
What is the next destination?
The summer nationwide tour 2025
PR Operation in...
Fukuoka!
The three of us are now in Fukuoka
What you can see behind us is...
The venue where we will perform
Marine Messe Fukuoka
It's amazing!
It's my first time seeing it from the outside
It's a strange shape
It's like a wave
It's ringing
And now we are...
We are on the ship!
It's shaking!
It's fun and feels good
We will perform in Fukuoka this time
It's famous in Fukuoka
I've never been on it before
So I wanted to try it
That's why I'm on it this time
Please go to the place where you are going
Is it called the sacred place?
Please enjoy the live performance
And enjoy Fukuoka
Let's enjoy it!
We are on the cruise
It's sudden
I have a recommendation for Fukuoka
Can I introduce it?
Of course!
Ta-da!
It's Kurowasu from Mikazuki
Kurowasu?
Yes, it's Kurowasu
I still buy it when I go back to Fukuoka
I always buy it
I always eat it before I go to Nogizaka
It has a lot of flavors
So I want to eat it for breakfast
Let's eat
What flavor do you like?
Black tea, soybean flour, and flan
By the way, I recommend soybean flour
I want to eat it because it's a recommendation
Can you eat it?
I can eat it
It looks delicious
Be careful not to spill it
Amazing
I recommend it to everyone
Please try it
It looks delicious
Let's eat
I can feel the soybean flour
It's delicious
It's a simple Kurowasu
Yes, it's simple
It's delicious
It's been a long time
Let's eat
It's delicious
Is there something in it?
There is soybean flour in it
Really?
It's delicious
What's wrong?
Soybean flour is in it
Be careful
Please try it
It's delicious
Did you come here often when you lived in Fukuoka?
I went to a shopping mall called Canal City
Do you know?
I've been there
I went to a shopping mall called Canal City
Really?
I went on a school trip
School trip?
In Fukuoka?
That's right
I saw the theater ceremony in Fukuoka
Did you see it?
I'm happy
I went to Fukuoka often
I didn't expect it
Oh, no
It's all over the place
It's cute
Mitsuki often spills
Really?
Does it look like an older sister?
It spills unexpectedly
I often see it spilling
It's cute
It spills a lot
It spills
It's so cute
There is a live performance on August 9th and 10th in Fukuoka
Please put it on as an announcement
I'll put it on later
Thank you
I moved to another place
I'm in Iwataya now
Here is my favorite
Mentai France bread
There is Fukutaro
I'm going to go there now
I'm looking forward to it
Let's go
I can see it
It says ME
I'm happy
It looks delicious
By the way, my recommendation is
Rich cheese
It must be delicious
This is very delicious
I'm not sure about this
I'll go with rich cheese
How is the plain one?
It's delicious
I've eaten this before
Rich plain
Mentai
It's full
It was delicious
What should I do?
I'm confused
How is it?
I'm curious about the cheese
I recommend the cheese
What do you think?
Please give me some advice
If you like simple food, I recommend the plain one
If you want to try something you haven't eaten before, I recommend the cheese
I'll go with the plain one
The plain one is good
Excuse me
I'll have two rich cheese and one plain
Thank you
What is this?
How many can I put in one?
I think I can do it
I'll start with the cheese
Thank you
How long does it take?
About 4 to 6 minutes
Okay
It's lined up
Do you usually warm it up here?
This is my first time to eat in
There is a freezer at the back of the house
I definitely bake it in the oven toaster when I come back
It's amazing
It's a continuation of bread
I'm sorry
I didn't think about anything
Why?
I put out a lot of my favorite bread
I'm sorry
Are the eyes of menbe?
I think so
The eyes of menbe are the same
Wait, isn't that right?
Menbe is in the back
Is it Mr. Kutaro?
The eyes of menbe
I've seen menbe before
It was the same eyes
The same eyes
I just found out
I love menbe
I love mentaiko
Wait
It seems to be 1 to 1.5 minutes
Is it burnt?
Is it okay?
It looks good
Thank you
It looks delicious
Please try it first
Is it okay?
Can I eat this?
Of course
Let's eat
It's delicious
It's cute
It's a guilty lobster
It's very delicious
There is something inside
There is cheese that melts
It's delicious
Let's eat
It's very delicious
I want you to eat cheese because it melts
Really?
It's very delicious
Let's eat
It's delicious
I've never eaten mentaiko bread
Really?
I ate it for the first time
It's delicious
If you eat it for the first time, you won't be able to eat anything else
That's true
Let's eat a lot of delicious food
There is a tour
Let's eat a lot
Nagizaka 46 will have a live performance in Fukuoka on August 9th and 10th
I would be happy if you could participate
Thank you
We have moved to Fukuoka
Speaking of Fukuoka
Mizutaki
It's a great place
We came to my favorite mizutaki restaurant
It's amazing
It's my first time going to this restaurant
I've been to other restaurants before
It was very delicious
Let's eat mizutaki together today
Let's go
We arrived at the seat
Today is a trip to eat
We've been here for a long time
How is your stomach?
It feels good, but the mizutaki part is empty
I'm glad
The mizutaki part is empty
Is it empty?
I also eat mizutaki
I'm glad
Everything that Miku-chan recommended was delicious
Really?
I'm glad
There are many dishes that suit your taste
This combination is not available
I was very nervous
I'm nervous too
It's here
It's amazing
It smells
The smell of the soup stock
It's an egg
It's shiny
Amazing
I will explain the dishes
This is a half-boiled egg
Please cut it from the middle
Please eat with mizutaki
Please open the dish
Thank you
There are seasonal ingredients
Fukuoka okura and myoga
It looks delicious
I really like okura
Okura is delicious
I like okura
Did you say bainiku?
Bainiku?
Ume
I like ume
I'm looking forward to it
I feel like a girlfriend no matter where I take it
My eyes are open
I will eat the egg
Please eat
I'm nervous
I'm nervous while watching
I'm watching
I'm talking
It's delicious
Delicious
Meat miso
It's sweet
Please eat okura
Can I eat okura?
I'm happy
Delicious
I can eat okura
Natsu
It's delicious
I think I like it
Please eat
I will eat
It's delicious
I'm sorry
I thought it was my sister
I'm glad to see that it looks like a child
First, please drink the soup as it is.
Thank you.
First, please close your eyes and drink the soup as it is.
It's hot, so please move to the side.
Close your eyes.
Itadakimasu.
It's hot.
It's delicious.
After drinking the soup,
we will prepare more ingredients.
Salt is the best salt in Itoshima City.
It's rich in minerals and has a strong umami.
What is salt?
It's a kind of chopsticks.
That's right.
Have you ever eaten Mitsutake?
Only once.
I have eaten Mitsutake in Fukuoka.
In Fukuoka?
Yes.
When?
I went to see Mr. Yoda's graduation concert.
I ate Mitsutake in Fukuoka on my way home.
Yuki came to Fukuoka with Yoda for two days.
I was glad to eat delicious food.
I ate Mitsutake with everyone. It was very delicious.
Next is meat and green onion shabu-shabu.
This is Hakata's all-purpose green onion.
It is boiled quickly.
This is meat.
This is from Kumamoto prefecture.
This is fresh meat.
This contains three types of breast, thigh, and bone.
This is homemade all-purpose ponzu sauce.
Please pour it little by little.
Thank you very much.
I will pour the ponzu sauce.
The color is different.
Thank you very much.
I will eat Mitsutake shabu-shabu.
Is it delicious?
It's the best.
It's soft.
Did you eat it?
I ate green onion.
I like green onion very much.
Me too.
It's very delicious.
Please eat it.
I will eat it.
It's delicious.
This is the best.
It's delicious and sweet.
This is Mitsuki's first tour.
How is it?
It's very fun.
Is it fun?
The food is different from the local food.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm glad.
Do you remember your first tour?
I remember it.
I was very nervous.
I'm glad that I'm enjoying it.
I was very nervous at first.
I was very nervous at the beginning.
As time went by, I was more and more excited.
Are you happy?
I'm looking forward to the new rock band.
I watched the rehearsal with Sakura for the first time.
Everyone is cute.
Miku was imitating the last pose.
I'm very happy.
Everyone is cute.
This is the last pose.
Is this pose meaningful?
Is this the 6th generation of rock band?
I don't know.
I don't know what this is.
Please tell me what you noticed.
I thought you noticed.
I didn't notice it.
That's the 6th generation of rock band.
There are a lot of rock bands in there.
That's true.
I'm happy.
Do Mitsuki and Miku usually talk?
I don't have a machine.
I didn't notice it.
I'm happy today.
I'm still nervous.
Do you two talk?
We used to do it together.
I have a chance to be with you.
I'm a good talker.
Did you go to a restaurant with your seniors?
I didn't go.
We're good friends.
We went to a restaurant for the second time.
We talked a lot.
I'm not good at talking.
I can't appeal to you.
Let's go next time.
What do you like?
I like anything.
Let's go somewhere together.
You haven't been out in the summer, have you?
You keep saying that.
Why do you know that?
It's always like that.
Let's go together next time.
Let's go.
You said it.
I'll invite you.
Will you really invite me?
Will you come if I invite you?
It's suspicious.
I'll go with you.
Let's go together.
Let's eat something that feels like summer.
I want to go.
It looks fun.
Please put your hands together.
Thank you for the meal.
We ate a lot of delicious food in Fukuoka.
It's over safely.
How was your day?
It was a short time.
I was able to enjoy Fukuoka.
I was able to eat delicious food that made me full.
I'm very satisfied.
That's good.
How was it?
Fukuoka was full of food.
It was delicious.
I'm looking forward to Fukuoka on the day of the concert.
Don't spill it in Fukuoka.
Be careful.
It was a rare three people.
They were cute and fun.
I was satisfied with my stomach and heart.
We are planning to have a concert in Sendai tomorrow.
We are in a hurry from now on.
We are in a hurry.
We will eat a lot of beef tongue tomorrow.
We will eat a lot.
Please subscribe to the channel and give us a high rating.
Thank you very much.
See you again.
Can I have this poster?
Yes, please.
Thank you very much.