Do you know about Nogizaka46 Talk App?
Oh, I'm late to introduce you.
I'm Iroha Okuda.
If you pay 350 yen per month,
There is a wonderful service that delivers photos, videos, and voices from the members.
In this video, I'm eating in the talk app.
I'm sending you a picture of me eating.
That was the popularity.
It turned out to be a YouTube project.
From now on, I will deliver it as usual.
I would be happy if you could take a look at it.
Then please.
Hello, I'm Iroha.
Today, I came to a Thai restaurant.
The interior of the store is colorful and cute.
I can't see much from this seat.
What I've prepared for this shoot is...
I'm very hungry.
I came here without eating breakfast.
I chose this restaurant because I was worried about the menu.
The timing to call the staff is always difficult.
One raw spring roll.
I want to order this.
Did you choose this?
Fried raw spring rolls.
Without this.
Thai omelet.
Do you want to eat this for one meal?
Then I'll have dessert later.
Do you want to eat it?
What should I choose?
What do you want to eat today?
It's my first time.
If I was alone, I wouldn't have eaten it.
What should I do?
There are a lot of drinks I've never seen before.
I'm going to try to get a stable drink.
It's a stable mango.
If I was alone, I wouldn't have ordered it.
I thought I had to do YouTube.
I ordered it with the spirit of a YouTuber.
It's delicious because it's sold in the store.
I usually start the video when I eat.
I was waiting for this time.
I checked the contents of the bag.
It's a letter set.
I'm into writing letters these days.
I'm writing.
I got a number.
I used to shoot with a tripod.
I couldn't get a picture of my hand.
I bought a tripod.
Thai omelet.
There's a bag on top.
There's a sauce on top.
It's very delicious.
A little spicy sauce and omelet.
It has a lot of soup.
It's thin, but it tastes good.
It was delicious.
This is fried raw spring rolls.
I ate it with soy sauce.
The outside is chewy.
The inside is similar to gyoza.
It was very delicious.
I have a very small mouth.
I eat a lot.
Fried raw spring rolls.
I felt a foreign country.
I don't know where I'm feeling it.
It was delicious with a taste that wasn't in Japan.
It's a Japanese-style mango.
It's finally here.
Fried raw spring rolls.
I've never eaten it before.
I was scared at first.
I said it was crispy, but it was okay.
I was worried.
It's very delicious.
It was delicious.
I was surprised.
The tip of the feet is crispy.
The part of the calf is like chicken.
It's more elastic than chicken.
It's like chicken.
It's delicious.
I was surprised.
The story changes completely.
At the beginning of this year, I went on a trip to Vietnam with Ioki Mao.
When I went to a place I didn't know, there were a lot of dishes I didn't know.
I met a lot of food.
I tried to put it in my mouth without fear.
I met a lot of delicious food.
I was happy.
I want to know a lot of food and go to a lot of countries.
Please tell me if there is a place that says it was delicious in this country.
I'm eating the potato I just got from Amane.
Tom Yum's potato.
I dropped the sauce.
It's like mango.
I'm pouring everything in.
I think I'm getting full.
I'm Hiroha.
I dropped the sauce.
I was wondering what was in the sauce.
I was researching.
I took a picture about a month ago.
I forgot what was in the sauce.
I'm sorry.
I think I'm done.
There was a lot of garbage around my mouth.
I couldn't get it off.
I looked at it and it was a mole.
How was it?
Please understand your own mole.
I came to a Thai restaurant this time.
I really like foreign food.
What is your favorite food?
I don't know.
When I choose a restaurant, I usually choose foreign food.
I want to eat food from other countries that I haven't eaten before.
I hope this project will continue if it is popular.
I'm full.
I thought I was going to get another meal.
I thought I was hungry.
I ordered everything.
My favorite food.
Fried banana.
I finally ordered dessert.
My favorite food is last spurt.
I always get sleepy when I eat.
I'm not good at fighting.
I ate all the vegetables.
Mango lassi and last spurt.
Even if you read it from above, it's cute.
Even if you read it from below, it's cute.
I like cameras.
I always put only one photo in this camera.
I took a picture of Mt. Fuji from the Shinkansen.
I look so sorry.
Finally, the fried banana is here.
I made it like this.
I put ice cream in the middle.
It's very delicious.
The outside is crispy.
The inside is hot.
There is a banana in it.
It goes well with ice cream.
It's so delicious that I miss it.
I want to eat it again.
I want to make it.
I want to make one banana at home.
It looks difficult.
It was really delicious.
However, as I said earlier, this is a cat's tongue.
I eat both.
It's hot and cold.
I ate while suffering.
After suffering, I realized that I could get something delicious and beautiful.
The video is coming to an end soon.
I sent you a video like this.
If you are interested, please come to the talk app in the morning.
Thank you for the meal.
See you.
Please subscribe to the channel and give it a high rating.
Good night.